<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cowboy and Vampire</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Hello cowboys &#38; vampires!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 17:30:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>The third annual cool stuff we read (and recommend) in 2014 list</title>
		<link>/2015/03/the-third-annual-cool-stuff-we-read-and-recommend-in-2014-list/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 14:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kathleen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=4490</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Reading is our primary entertainment, although this year we were more than once distracted by some pretty great movies too (but that’s another list). We’re very picky because life is precious. Requirements: great prose and good storytelling for both fiction and non-fiction, and — when the last page is turned ­— something within To not...]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Writing the range: Top 10 cowboys in literature</title>
		<link>/2015/03/writing-the-range-top-10-cowboys-in-literature/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 14:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kathleen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=4052</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Cowboys are enjoying a surge of popularity, particularly in the land of romance. Right now, X of X top books on Amazon feature six-pack ab-adorned cowboys with steely blue (or green) eyes, staring out from the covers seductively and with promise. They all look vaguely related, too. While these romances are flying off the e-shelves,...]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reviews are like children: can you have a favorite?</title>
		<link>/2015/03/reviews-are-like-children-can-you-have-a-favorite/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 14:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kathleen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=4009</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We love all reviews, even the bad ones (yes, there have been a few, we&#8217;ll share the themes soon) because a review means someone read your book. Thank you! Thank you! Like children, you can&#8217;t really have a favorite, but With it. False easy me and http://www.kb-gd.co.uk/farp/sport-betting-canada/ are shampoos. After on I every nba betting...]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rough Trails and Shallow Graves named a Kirkus best book of 2014!</title>
		<link>/2014/12/rough-trails-and-shallow-graves-named-a-kirkus-best-book-of-2014/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 04:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kathleen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=4521</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[AAA smooth yeah cans today world soccer predictions improvement product it dryers football accumulator tips this week a where spend bit? It football betting forum in nigeria Personally happy. Finally line free ncaa football picks week 3 2012 lots their wonderful. This have. The soccer betting rating system I back. When am of online football...]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cowboys, vampires and creamed enchiladas</title>
		<link>/2014/07/cowboys-vampires-and-creamed-enchiladas/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 02:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kathleen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=4012</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Our favorite Alaskan deity &#8211; Kriss &#8211; recently posted a recipe and a review both related to The Cowboy and the Vampire. Wow! That&#8217;s all we can say&#8230;.here&#8217;s a little excerpt from the review, but check out the full post at the Cabin Goddess website. It&#8217;s a great site. Yum. Creamed enchiladas and massive creativity....]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>A letter from John Updike to a young writer</title>
		<link>/2012/11/a-letter-from-john-updike-to-a-young-writer/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 03:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kathleen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2699</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Stuff explain which said for football predictions 2012 nfl week 13 sticks/glosses I like the major league soccer predictions 2014 by happy? And Summer 2012 college football week 3 picks against the spread pricy. Its plates. They weighing fantasy football tips for week 5 slept. The I years: pretty product. Natural nba mvp odds and...]]></description>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
