<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>Comments for Cowboy and Vampire</title>
	<atom:link href="/comments/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Hello cowboys &#38; vampires!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 03:11:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>Comment on Ask a Cowboy by Dear Cowboy: Cowboy wisdom from author Clark Hays &#124; Pumpjack Press</title>
		<link>/ask-a-cowboy/comment-page-1/#comment-23393</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dear Cowboy: Cowboy wisdom from author Clark Hays &#124; Pumpjack Press]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 03:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?page_id=6#comment-23393</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[[&#8230;] the world, and readers are responding, wanting a taste of their own cowboy wisdom. Check out the Ask-a-Cowboy column over at the author&#8217;s website.  The questions are, unsurprisingly, mostly about love in [&#8230;]]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[&#8230;] the world, and readers are responding, wanting a taste of their own cowboy wisdom. Check out the Ask-a-Cowboy column over at the author&#8217;s website.  The questions are, unsurprisingly, mostly about love in [&#8230;]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Comment on Climbing Goat Mountain: When art imitates life by Author perspective: When art imitates life &#124; Pumpjack Press</title>
		<link>/soapbox/climbing-goat-mountain-when-art-imitates-life/comment-page-1/#comment-20428</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Author perspective: When art imitates life &#124; Pumpjack Press]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2014 18:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=writinglifepost&#038;p=3958#comment-20428</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[[&#8230;] of killing, gutting deer; art imitates life. Goat Mountain kindles PTSD of childhood #hunting.  cowboyandvampire.com/soapbox/climbi… #MondayBlogs [&#8230;]]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[&#8230;] of killing, gutting deer; art imitates life. Goat Mountain kindles PTSD of childhood #hunting.  cowboyandvampire.com/soapbox/climbi… #MondayBlogs [&#8230;]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Comment on Queasy rider: voyage of the damned by valerie</title>
		<link>/soapbox/queasy-rider-voyage-of-the-damned/comment-page-1/#comment-6777</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[valerie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 04:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=writinglifepost&#038;p=3786#comment-6777</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[is this the newest weight loss fad? hilarious!!]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>is this the newest weight loss fad? hilarious!!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Comment on Surges, sacrificial rats and near-death by Keeping it real &#124; Pumpjack Press</title>
		<link>/soapbox/surges-sacrificial-rats-and-near-death/comment-page-1/#comment-126</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keeping it real &#124; Pumpjack Press]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 19:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=writinglifepost&#038;p=3423#comment-126</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[[&#8230;] ensure their fiction resonates with reality? They track scientific literature.  Here&#8217;s a new post from author Kathleen McFall about the cultural implications of a recent University of [&#8230;]]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[&#8230;] ensure their fiction resonates with reality? They track scientific literature.  Here&#8217;s a new post from author Kathleen McFall about the cultural implications of a recent University of [&#8230;]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Comment on Are serial killers sexy? by Clark H.</title>
		<link>/soapbox/are-serial-killers-sexy/comment-page-1/#comment-121</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Clark H.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 18:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=writinglifepost&#038;p=3388#comment-121</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It just so happens I&#039;m reading a book -- Cruelty: Human Evil and the Human Brain (by Kathleen Taylor) that explores the neurologic, biologic and social/cultural sources behind the impulse to be cruel. The chapter I just finished discuses her theory of why we glamorize sadism in movies and fiction. She sees three basic reasons that &quot;the most popular fiction reassures us, just as religions do,&quot; about sadism. It shows us that:

1) we have particular meaning and importance to others (even when they hate us)
2) cruelty is punished
3) and evil people are alien (to us)
She makes a compelling case that evil, sadistic characters let us experience the thrill of breaking social norms (because one must be strong and powerful and confident and smart) with not risk of the inevitable social and legal ramifications (being ostracized and/or imprisoned and/or killed). We identify with and long for their power, vicariously. Plus, she argues that negative emotions (fear, disgust, cruelty, sadism, callousness, etc.) are all more powerfully distinguished in the neural pathways. Having a cup of tea is rewarding and wonderful, but leaves no echo of its passing. Reading the horrible things Hannibal Lecter does gets our neurons all fired up with moralizing and fear and squirmy pleasure and vicarious thrills and the hope he will be caught and thinking about how we would react if we were confronted with that situation and wondering if we could ever do something like that or if we would be smart enough to catch him, etc.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It just so happens I&#8217;m reading a book &#8212; Cruelty: Human Evil and the Human Brain (by Kathleen Taylor) that explores the neurologic, biologic and social/cultural sources behind the impulse to be cruel. The chapter I just finished discuses her theory of why we glamorize sadism in movies and fiction. She sees three basic reasons that &#8220;the most popular fiction reassures us, just as religions do,&#8221; about sadism. It shows us that:</p>
<p>1) we have particular meaning and importance to others (even when they hate us)<br />
2) cruelty is punished<br />
3) and evil people are alien (to us)<br />
She makes a compelling case that evil, sadistic characters let us experience the thrill of breaking social norms (because one must be strong and powerful and confident and smart) with not risk of the inevitable social and legal ramifications (being ostracized and/or imprisoned and/or killed). We identify with and long for their power, vicariously. Plus, she argues that negative emotions (fear, disgust, cruelty, sadism, callousness, etc.) are all more powerfully distinguished in the neural pathways. Having a cup of tea is rewarding and wonderful, but leaves no echo of its passing. Reading the horrible things Hannibal Lecter does gets our neurons all fired up with moralizing and fear and squirmy pleasure and vicarious thrills and the hope he will be caught and thinking about how we would react if we were confronted with that situation and wondering if we could ever do something like that or if we would be smart enough to catch him, etc.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Comment on Are serial killers sexy? by kathleen</title>
		<link>/soapbox/are-serial-killers-sexy/comment-page-1/#comment-100</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kathleen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 21:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=writinglifepost&#038;p=3388#comment-100</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Lisa, thanks for the comment. Really interesting points! I agree with all of them, and your perspective alludes to the other question I called out. Can we meet the same literary/story-telling goals and accompanying psychic exploration without &quot;real&quot; people? For example, the vampire myth (in its original form) and other supernatural figures permit this but without the requisite pseudo-glorification of human-on-human violence.  -KM
(PS: And where did you read that article about the uncanny valley? I&#039;d like to read it too.)]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lisa, thanks for the comment. Really interesting points! I agree with all of them, and your perspective alludes to the other question I called out. Can we meet the same literary/story-telling goals and accompanying psychic exploration without &#8220;real&#8221; people? For example, the vampire myth (in its original form) and other supernatural figures permit this but without the requisite pseudo-glorification of human-on-human violence.  -KM<br />
(PS: And where did you read that article about the uncanny valley? I&#8217;d like to read it too.)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Comment on Are serial killers sexy? by Lisa F.</title>
		<link>/soapbox/are-serial-killers-sexy/comment-page-1/#comment-99</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lisa F.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 15:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=writinglifepost&#038;p=3388#comment-99</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Are serial killers sexy? From a writer&#039;s standpoint, they need to be depicted as sexy or ingenious or otherwise superior for a number of reasons. A protagonist needs a certain level of likeability - hence attractive features or mental prowess. Even as an antagonist, the killer needs to be deemed worth chasing and eliminating. On a more human level though, depicted serial killers represent a part of us that we wish we had: the ability to outsmart anyone, charm and charisma, the ability to make a game of what would be a stressful situation, the seeming lack of stress response to stressful situations. Simply, the air of control over one&#039;s environment. 

I recently read an article about the &quot;Uncanny Valley&quot;, that part of the spectrum between unrealistic human depiction, such as cartoons and Claymation, and lifelike - human. There is a valley in the graph which shows that just before a human depiction becomes the most lifelike, it becomes creepy. The depiction that is almost human is frightening to people, much more-so than the inhuman monsters in even the best horror fiction. The concept of a serial killer that is attractive (and creepy) is that by the time the uncanny valley is revealed, it&#039;s too late. What a helpful man, helping me with my flat tire. And he&#039;s good-looking, too. What did he just say? What size clothing do I wear? Oops! I&#039;m done for. 

Does the attraction translate to real killers? Only to the extent that people take enjoyment in figuring out the puzzle. We need to profile this person, put them in a neat package, so that they don&#039;t outsmart US. That&#039;s the play-at-home game. To most people, there is nothing sexy about actual serial murder, but the safety of fiction allows us to peek inside and safely play with the parts of it that are super-, sub-, exra-human.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are serial killers sexy? From a writer&#8217;s standpoint, they need to be depicted as sexy or ingenious or otherwise superior for a number of reasons. A protagonist needs a certain level of likeability &#8211; hence attractive features or mental prowess. Even as an antagonist, the killer needs to be deemed worth chasing and eliminating. On a more human level though, depicted serial killers represent a part of us that we wish we had: the ability to outsmart anyone, charm and charisma, the ability to make a game of what would be a stressful situation, the seeming lack of stress response to stressful situations. Simply, the air of control over one&#8217;s environment. </p>
<p>I recently read an article about the &#8220;Uncanny Valley&#8221;, that part of the spectrum between unrealistic human depiction, such as cartoons and Claymation, and lifelike &#8211; human. There is a valley in the graph which shows that just before a human depiction becomes the most lifelike, it becomes creepy. The depiction that is almost human is frightening to people, much more-so than the inhuman monsters in even the best horror fiction. The concept of a serial killer that is attractive (and creepy) is that by the time the uncanny valley is revealed, it&#8217;s too late. What a helpful man, helping me with my flat tire. And he&#8217;s good-looking, too. What did he just say? What size clothing do I wear? Oops! I&#8217;m done for. </p>
<p>Does the attraction translate to real killers? Only to the extent that people take enjoyment in figuring out the puzzle. We need to profile this person, put them in a neat package, so that they don&#8217;t outsmart US. That&#8217;s the play-at-home game. To most people, there is nothing sexy about actual serial murder, but the safety of fiction allows us to peek inside and safely play with the parts of it that are super-, sub-, exra-human.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Comment on Ask a Cowboy by Ask a Cowboy &#171; Pumpjack Press</title>
		<link>/ask-a-cowboy/comment-page-1/#comment-33</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ask a Cowboy &#171; Pumpjack Press]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?page_id=6#comment-33</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[[...] but I don’t know what’s wrong with him. He has been acting different. More distant &#8230; Read more &#062;&#062; Share [...]]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[&#8230;] but I don’t know what’s wrong with him. He has been acting different. More distant &#8230; Read more &gt;&gt; Share [&#8230;]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
